# VITOR LUIGI ORSINI SILVA

## **Software Engineer**

Address: Siderurgia, Ouro Branco, MG - Brazil ZIP: 36492-192

📠 linkedin.com/in/vitorluigiorsini 🔝 github.com/vitorluigiorsini 😵 https://vitororsini.vercel.app

#### RESUME

Major in Civil Engineering. Developer and Computer Technician with more than 5 years of experience in IT. Experience as a professor of hardware and software, computer maintenance manager and IT technical assistant. Lived in the United States for 18 months. Have advanced fluency in English. Acting since September 2021 in the technology area. Currently working as a Full Stack Developer in a startup.

#### SKILLS\_

- JavaScript | TypeScript | NodeJs | Express | React | Ruby | Ruby on Rails | HTML | CSS | Git
- SQL | NoSQL | MySQL | PostgreSQL | MongoDB | DynamoDB
- Cloud computing | CI/CD | AWS | Serverless | Docker
- Methodologies: Agile | Scrum | Kanban

#### EXPERIENCE

## Full Stack Developer | Ctrl Saúde | 09/2022 - Current

- Project management with agile methodology (Kanban).
- Implementation of systems with the main technologies: AWS, NodeJs, TypeScript and React.
- Backend: implementation of Rest API, integration with external APIs, serverless framework.
- Frontend: implementation of user interfaces with React and Material UI.

## Civil Engineer | MCA Auditoria e Gerenciamento Ltda | 08/2021 - 03/2022

- Inspection of engineering services in CAPEX study projects.
- Follow-up of technical inspections and structural integrity assessment.
- Schedule planning and monitoring.
- Survey of documentation for release of activities.
- Verification of technical documentation.

### EDUCATION

## Bachelor of Engineering | Universidade Federal de São João del-Rei (UFSJ) | 08/2011 - 02/2018

• Major in Civil Engineering

## Technician | Colégio Batista Mineiro de Ouro Branco | 02/2003 - 12/2005

Computer Technician

#### OTHERS

- English Advanced level
- Exchange EUA (03/2014 06/2015)
- Agile Project Planning and Management (end forecast: 06/2023)
- AWS Serverless application + Typescript and NodeJs 2023
- JavaScript, TypeScript, NodeJs, React 2022